So y'all know I don't play about a couple things. I don't play about voting. I don't play about
black folks, okay? And I don't play about bonobos. It has been giving day for apes for about three
weeks. I know it's day, but it's days, okay? And the truth is, is that a lot of people do not know
about bonobos. And you also don't know about Lola Ya Bonobo, which is a reserve where they are
rehabilitating and releasing bonobos into the wild in the Democratic Republic of Congo.
In order for them to do this, they have to work in partnership with the community. And
unfortunately, a couple months ago, there was violence that took place at Ecole Ya Bonobo
Community Reserve. Two bonobos were actually killed and a number of the facilities were burned down.
Nonetheless, people are working together within the community and within Lola Ya Bonobo to bring
things back to life. And you can also help this happen. You can donate and support and you can
spread the word. Because I believe that we have to take care of our environment. We have to take
care of all that's within our environment. And that's not just us, the people. That's also our
very close neighbors to people, the bonobo, which shares 98.7% of our DNA. And we can also learn a lot
from their community because they don't even fight no more, y'all. They fix everything with love.
To learn more, go to friendsofbonobos.org or follow Lola Ya Bonobo.